(Sheldon:)Now, I don't see me
as some four-star general back at HQ...
...riding a desk and playing goIf
with the Secretary of Defense.
(Sheldon:)But I also can't be Sergeant Cooper
because that might lead you...
...to think of me as a regular Joe. This
might take some thought. As you were.
- What the hell is wrong with you?
- How could you do that?
(Raj:)Yeah, right.
You're jealous because...
...I'm Penny's number-two choice
after Leonard.
(Howard:)Hey, if I wasn't engaged to Bernadette,
that totally could have been me.
Please. Sheldon would've
been before you...
(Leonard:)...and he might not even
have genitals.
(Raj:)Why do you care so much?
You're dating my sister...
(Raj:)...and Penny and I are in love.
- What, heh?
- What?
(Sheldon:)Gentlemen, if I may interject.
(Sheldon:)I've decided my rank will be captain.
(Sheldon:)If it's good enough for Kirk,
Crunch and Kangaroo...
(Sheldon:)...it's good enough for me.
- You're not in Iove with Penny.
- Yes, I am.
(Raj:)The god Kamadeva has shot us
with his flowery arrows of love.